(Sheldon:)I shook my booty
to the seductive rhythms...
(Penny:)Okay, okay.
(Shldon:)...of AP Calculus.
(Raj:)How come you're not shopping
with Amy and Bernadette?
(Leonard:)Let me guess, you think
the whole idea is lame?
(Penny:)Well, who cares what I think?
What do you think?
(Leonard:)Hmm, to be honest,
(Leonard:)it's kind of a dream come true
to go to even a fake prom
(Leonard:)with a woman
as beautiful as you.
(Penny:)Ugh, thanks a lot.
(Leonard:)What?
(Penny:)Well, now I can't blow this
thing off without being a bitch.
That sounds like a "yes"!
(Bernadette:)Ooh, every single person
RSVP'd "yes."
This is so exciting!
(higher pitched):
Isn't this exciting?
(dog howls)
(Howard:)Yep.
(Bernadette:)Look, even Stuart's
bringing a date.
(Bernadette:)I wonder who it is.
(Howard:)You know exactly
who it is.
(Howard:)He's gonna bring my mom.
(Howard:)Why did you even invite him?
(Bernadette:)Because he's our friend,
and you two need to get along.
(Bernadette:)And why can't
he take your mom?